{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "JsFunctions",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "A function that calls itself ?",
      "correct_answer": "A recursive function",
      "q_source": "developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Glossary/Function",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "XX",
        "YY",
        "ZZ"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "JsFunctions",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "These functions run as soon as they are defined and are identified by an extra set of parenthesis at the end of their definition.?",
      "correct_answer": "Immediately Invoked Function Expressions (IIFEs)",
      "q_source": "developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Glossary/IIFE",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "XX",
        "YY",
        "ZZ"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "JsFunctions",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "which ?",
      "correct_answer": "Zealand",
      "q_source": "w3schools",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "XX",
        "YY",
        "ZZ"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "JsFunctions",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Term for when the interpreter appears to move the declaration of functions, variables or classes to the top of their scope, prior to execution of the code. ?",
      "correct_answer": "Hoisting",
      "q_source": "developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Glossary/Hoisting",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "XX",
        "YY",
        "ZZ"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "JsFunctions",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "3 basic kinds of scope in Javascript include Function scope, Module scope and this default scope for all code running in script mode ?",
      "correct_answer": "Global scope",
      "q_source": "developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Glossary/Scope",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "XX",
        "YY",
        "ZZ"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "JsFunctions",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "which ?",
      "correct_answer": "Zealand",
      "q_source": "w3schools",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "XX",
        "YY",
        "ZZ"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "JsFunctions",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "which ?",
      "correct_answer": "Zealand",
      "q_source": "w3schools",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "XX",
        "YY",
        "ZZ"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "JsFunctions",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The scope created with a pair of curly braces ?",
      "correct_answer": "Block scope",
      "q_source": "developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Glossary/Scope",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "XX",
        "YY",
        "ZZ"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "JsFunctions",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Although they are similar, call() accepts an argument list, but apply() accepts a single one of these ?",
      "correct_answer": "Array of arguments",
      "q_source": "developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/JavaScript/Reference/Global_Objects/Function/apply",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "XX",
        "YY",
        "ZZ"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "JsFunctions",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "This operator is used to pause and resume a generator function. ?",
      "correct_answer": "Yield",
      "q_source": "developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/JavaScript/Reference/Operators/yield",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "XX",
        "YY",
        "ZZ"
      ]
    }
  ]
}